Button, Daniel Evan; Papers apap231
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Correspondence, 1966-1970; Undated; 3; 12.8 cubic ft.
  - Electoral reform, 1969-1970 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Eliminating hunger, 1969 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Employment, 1967-1968 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 6-7)
  - Environment, 1969-1970 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Environmental control - insertion, 1970 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Environmental decade of the 70s, 1969 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Ethics in congress and congressional reform, 1967-1968 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Extensions of interstate route I - 88, 1969-1970 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Fair Labeling and Packaging Act, 1967 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Far East, 1969 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Farm legislation, 1970 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - FCC and AT&T agreement, includes newsclipping, 1969 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Federal employees, 1967 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Federal job applications, Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Federal spending, 1967 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Firearms, 1967 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Firearms bill, 1968-1969 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 21-22)
  - 5 dollar vote, 1967 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Flag bill, 1967 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Food stamp program, 1967-1968 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Foreign aid, 1968-1970 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Foreign affairs, 1967-1970 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 27-28)
  - Foreign policy and defense spending, 1969 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Foreign visitors, 1967 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - French Middle East policy, 1970; Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - General Acknowledgement, 1967 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 32-35)
  - General Acknowledgement, 1968 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 36-37)
  - General Acknowledgement, 1969 (Box 4 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 38-39)
  - General Acknowledgement, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 1-3)
  - General Acknowledgement, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - General clinical research centers, 1970; Undated (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - General file, - no carbons, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - General inquiry, 1968-1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - General - newsletter response, 1968 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - George Wallace, 1967; Undated (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Great Lakes Basin Compact, 1967 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Headstart program, 1968; Undated (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Health - drugs, 1967-1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 12-13)
  - Highway 99, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Higway funds cut - back, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Holiday bill, 1967 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Holidays and days of commemoration, 1968 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Honorary memberships, 1967 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Housing and Urban Development, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - H.R. inquiries, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - H.R. 337 per diem allowance for government employees on business, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - H.R. 6780 workmen's compensation, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - H.R. 9010 TIAA - CREF, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - H.R. 10249 100% retirement for National Guard employees, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - H.R. 11607 railroad employees, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 25-26)
  - H.R. 11620, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - H.R. 11750 post office out of district comments, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - H.R. 11792 "Salty Israel", 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - H.R. 11870 big trucks, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - H.R. 12025 National Timber Supply Act, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - H.R. 13300, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - HUAC, 1967 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - H.U.D., 1967-1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - I - 88 letters, answered, 1969; Undated (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - I - 88 moving north, 1969-1970; Undated (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - I - 88 petition, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - "Importance of Apples Noted" - record insert, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Inaugural license plates, 1968 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Independeant maritime agency, 1967 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Individual requests, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 41-42)
  - Inflation - answered, 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Inflation - federal spending, 1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Insurance, 1968 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Insurance - riot insurance, 1968 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 46)
  - INTELSAT channels by U.N., 1969 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 47)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1967-1968 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Interns, 1967-1970 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 49)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1967 (Box 5 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 50)
  - Inquries and requests, 1968; 1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 1-2)
  - Inquries and requests - flags, 1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Investment credit, 1969 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Investment credit tax, 1967 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Invitation - regrets, 1969-1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Invitation responses, 1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Invitation to meet John H.G. Callahan, 1968 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Invitation, regrets, 1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Israel and Middle East, 1970; Undated (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Israel letters - answered, 1967; 1969-1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 11-12)
  - Israel telegrams, 1967 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Israel telegrams and letters, 1967; Undated (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Israel relations telegrams, 1967 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Judiciary, 1967-1968 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Labor, 1968-1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 17-18)
  - Labor hearings, 1967 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Latin America, 1967 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Legislation, 1968 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 21-22)
  - Legislation, 1969 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 23-25)
  - Legislation, 1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 26-27)
  - Legislation - responses, 1967 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Letters to chairman of oil import task force, 1969 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Letters to director of OEO, Donald Rumsfeld - regarding fellowship, 1969 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Letter to president concerning "MIRV", 1969 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Letter to Senator Albert Gore on tax reform, 1969 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Letters, 1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Letters to Republican elect, 1969 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Local cases, 1967 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Medicaid, 1967-1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Members, 1967 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Members of Congress, 1969 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries, 1967-1970 (Box 6 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Messages, 1967 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Middle East, 1970 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Military, 1967 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Military budget, 1970 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous, 1966-1967 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 5-7)
  - Miscellaneous general, 1968 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Moving expense tax, 1967 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - National Guard, 1966-1967 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - National Guard Technician Act, 1970 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - National Parks and Recreation, 1967-1968 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - National Timber Act - answered, 1970 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Neighborhood youth corps projects - telegram, 1969 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - New HEW sustain letter, 1970 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - New I - 88 interstate letters, 1969 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 16-17)
  - New resident, 1967; 1969 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - New York State, 1966-1967 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Newsletter, 1967 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Nigerian crisis, 1970; Undated (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - No answer, 1967 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 22-23)
  - No further reply, 1966 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - No name, 1967-1968 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Nuclear policy, 1967 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - OEO, 1967-1969 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 27-28)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1969-1970 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Office operations, 1968 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - One bank holding company, 1969 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Opposition Combodia letters - to Button, 1970 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Original 11750 Letter, post office, 1969 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Organized crime, 1970 (Box 7 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Out of district comments of H.R. 1300 - postal pay, 1970 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Out of district mail, 1967-1970 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 2-4)
  - Pages for Congress, 1966-1967 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Patented water pump purifier, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Pay TV Letters, answered, 1969 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Peace marchers lodgings, 1969 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Petition supporting the amendment to end the Vietnam War, 1970 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Political, 1967-1970 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 10-11)
  - Pollution - air and water, 1969-1970 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Pollution - answered, 1969-1970 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Pollution - kiddy letters, 1969-1970 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Population control measures, 1970 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Post office, 1970 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Post office committee, 1968-1969 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Post office constituent legislation, 1969 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 18-19)
  - Post office department, 1968-1970 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 20-22)
  - Post office - legialation, 1968-1970 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 23-24)
  - Postal clerks, 1968-1969 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Postal Reform "compromise", 1969-1970 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Postal reform letters (answered), 1970 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Postal Service Act, 1969 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Prayer, no answer, 1966-1967 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Press, 1967; 1969 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 30-31)
  - Pro - ABM deplayment, 1969 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Pro - Button on Cambodia - answered, 1970 (Box 8 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 33-35)
  - Pro - Cambodian Involvment - answered, 1970 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Pro - Wixan reject (not answered), 1970; Undated (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Public works, 1967 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Pueblo Incident, 1969 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - "Queen Isabella Day" - extension of remarks, 1970 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Questionnaire, 1967; 1970 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 6-7)
  - Questionnaire: causes of rioting, 1967 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Questionnaire general acknowledgement, 1970 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Questionnaire release to media, press release, 1968 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Questionnaire report newsletter, 1967 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Questionnaire results - press release, 1967 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Questionnaires, 1967 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 13-16)
  - Questionnaires, 1969 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Questionnaires with letters, 1970 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Quotes, 1968; Undated (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Radio and TV, 1968-1970 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Railroad letter, Undated (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Railroad retirement, 1970 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Railroads, 1967 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Rat extermination funds, 1967 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Receptions, 1969; Undated (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Record Insert - Commissioner Allen, 1970 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Record Insert - Hospital volunteers, 1970 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Redistricting, 1967 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Reducing aircraft noise, 1970 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Refer, 1968 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Religious Affairs, 1967 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - Republicans for Congress, 1967 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - Request - organizations, 1970 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Request - school project, 1970 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - Requests, 1967 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 35-38)
  - Requests, 1969 (Box 9 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 39-40)
  - Requests, 1969 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Requests, 1970 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Requests from organizations, 1969 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Requests - general, 1968 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Requests - out of district, 1966-1967 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Requests - publications, 1968 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - Requests - Schenectady, 1967 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Requests - school projects, 1968-1969 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Reserve Forces, Bill of Rights, 1967 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Riots, 1967-1968 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Ripon Society, 1967 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Robert Kennedy Memorial, 1969 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - Rush Bagot, 1968 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - S. 952 Federal judges ominibus bill, 1969; Undated (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - S. 2218 High school equivalency diploma, 1970 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - "Save the Bozen Kill" - extension of remarks, 1970 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Science and astronautics, 1967 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Scotia Glenville High School tour, 1970 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Seal furs, 1970 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Second HEW sustain letter, 1970 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Second 11730 letter, 1969-1970 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1967 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - "Seizure of Baltics Recalled" - record insertion, 1970 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Selective Service, 1967-1968 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 24-25)
  - Senator Goodell's Vietnam resolution, 1969 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Senator response, Undated (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Shoe import quotas, 1969 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Situs - picketing, 1967 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Small Business Administration, 1967 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Social Security, 1967-1970 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 31-34)
  - Social Security Benefits, 1969 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Society for Autistic Children, 1967 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - South Africa, 1963; 1966-1967; Undated (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Soviet build up in the Middle East, bipartisan appeal, 1970 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - Space program, 1970 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Special letters, 1967-1969 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 40)
  - Special messages, congratulations and thank yous, 1970; Undated (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 41)
  - Special telephone inquiries with federal departments and agencies on behalf of constituents, 1969; Undated (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 42)
  - Sponsors, 1967 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Staff, 1967 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Statement on lecture by D.K. Hardy in Albany - press release, 1967; Undated (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 45)
  - Statement on Lithuanian Independence Observance - insertion, 1970 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 46)
  - Statement regarding visit with 1018th service and supply company at Fort Lee, Virginia, Undated (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 47)
  - Stockade, S00D Affair, 1969; Undated (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Student loan labor H.E.W appropriation - unanswered, 1970 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 49)
  - Student loan letters, answered, 1970 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 50)
  - Students, 1970 (Box 10 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 51)
  - Summer job, 1969-1970 (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Supersonic transport, 1969 (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Support charitable organizations, Undated (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Surtax, 1969 (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Sustain HEW bill, 1970 (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 5)
  - Sympathy, 1967-1969 (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - TAP proposal, 1970 (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - Tariff, 1967 (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Tax, 1968 (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Tax bill, 1967 (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Tax reform, 1969-1970 (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 11-13)
  - Tax reform insert, 1969 (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Tax - surtax, 1968 (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Taxes - general, 1969-1970 (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Taxes - reform, 1969 (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Telegram to Frank Smith, Undated (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Telegrams, Undated (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Textile Industry tariffs, Nixon, 1968; 1970 (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Thank you, 1967 (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 21-22)
  - Thank you letters from DEB, 1968 (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Thank you letters from DEB, 1969 (Box 11 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 24-26)
  - Thank you letters from DEB, 1969 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 1-2)
  - Thank you letters from DEB, 1970 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Thank you to DEB, 1968-1970 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 4-5)
  - Thin Blue Line, 1967 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 6)
  - "A Thirty Year Struggle for Freedom" - record insert, 1970 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 7)
  - To Daniel Button, 1968-1969 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 8)
  - Trade, 1967 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 9)
  - Travel restrictions, 1968 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 10)
  - Truth in lending, 1967-1968 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 11)
  - Tuition tax credit, 1967 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 12)
  - TWA Jet Hijacking, 1969 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Unanswered gun referrals, 1968 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 14-15)
  - Unanswered mail, 1969-1970 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 16-17)
  - Unions, 1967 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - United Nations, 1967 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - Urban Affairs, 1967-1968 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - U.S. China relations, 1969 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - U.S.I.A., 1967 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - U.S. Oceans policy, 1970 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Veteran scholarship letters, 1967 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - Veterans, 1968; Undated (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Veterans affairs, 1968; 1970 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - Veterans benefits, 1967 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Veterans Day, "Day of national concern" - letter to Nixon, 1969 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - "Veterans health care" - extension of remarks, 1970 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Vietnam, 1967-1970 (Box 12 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 30-32)
  - Vietnam, 1967-1970 (Box 13 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Vietnam and Cambodia, 1970 (Box 13 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 2)
  - Vietnam Correspondence, 1967 (Box 13 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 3)
  - Vietnam War Moratorium, 1969 (Box 13 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 4)
  - Visitors, 1967-1970 (Box 13 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 5-8)
  - VITA, 1969 (Box 14 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 1)
  - Volunteers, 1967 (Box 14 (3-Subject Correspondence), Folder 2)